{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is the expected monetary loss of a security risk with an asset value (AV) of Â£100,000 and an exposure factor (EF) of 0.2, i.e., the single loss expectancy?",
            "correctAnswer": "20000",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What form of cyberattack is it when an attacker is attempting to deceive individuals by sending fake emails that appear to be from a trusted source, asking for personal information like passwords and financial details?",
            "correctAnswer": "Phishing",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does CIA stand for?",
            "correctAnswer": "Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which term refers to malware that uses encryption to hold a victim's data at ransom, demanding payment for decryption?",
            "correctAnswer": "Ransomware",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which term refers to when an attacker gains access to a wireless network and eavesdrops on the communication between two devices?",
            "correctAnswer": "Eavesdropping",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is it called when a cybercriminal floods a legitimate website with fabricated requests?",
            "correctAnswer": "DDoS, DoS",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "What form of cyberattack is it called when an attacker repeatedly attempts various passwords until the correct one is found?",
            "correctAnswer": "Brute force attack, brute force",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "If an employee recieves an email with a suspicious attachment and opens it - what type of threat is this?",
            "correctAnswer": "Malware",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "According to the lecture, what is an example of a (potential) asset?",
            "correctAnswer": "Money, Physical, Assets, Information, Facilities, People, Reputation, Intangibles",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which type of security attack involves altering a program, such as the introduction of viruses?",
            "correctAnswer": "Modification, Modification attack",
            "incorrectAnswer1": "A",
            "incorrectAnswer2": "B",
            "incorrectAnswer3": "C"
        }
        
        

        
        




        

    ]
}